Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. International Advertisements Collection, 1900-2004 and undated, bulk 1965-1990
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Canada Series, 1921-1997 and undated (Box AP10)
  - Montreal Office (Box AP10)
    - Kraft (See also Oversize Box OV4) (Box CA8)
      - Miscellaneous and multiple products (Box CA9)
        - Consumer magazine, 1976-1990, (9 folders) (Box CA10)
        - Consumer newspaper, 1943-1962, (9 folders) (Box CA10)
        - Consumer newspaper, 1963-1979, (5 folders) (Box CA11)
        - Trade magazine, 1943-1979, (10 folders) (Box CA11)
    - Labatt (See also Oversize Folder OF11) (Box CA12)
      - Consumer magazine, 1958-1979, (4 folders) (Box CA12)
      - Consumer newspaper, 1958-1979, (14 folders) (Box CA12)
      - Trade magazine, 1958-1967, (2 folders) (Box CA12)
    - Loyola of Montreal, consumer newspaper, 1967 (Box CA13)
    - LTV Ling Altec, trade magazine, 1971 (Box CA13)
    - Mars, trade magazine, 1970 (Box CA13)
    - McDonnell Douglas (Box CA13)
      - Consumer magazine, 1959-1978 (Box CA13)
      - Consumer newspaper, 1958-1979, (2 folders) (Box CA13)
      - Trade magazine, 1957-1979, (5 folders) (Box CA13)
      - Trade newspaper, 1968-1979 (Box CA13)
    - McGuinness liqueur, consumer magazine, 1978 (Box CA13)
    - Merrill Lynch, Pierce, Fenner, and Smith (Box CA13)
      - Consumer magazine, 1962-1965 (Box CA13)
      - Consumer newspaper, 1962-1965 (Box CA13)
    - Metcalfe House, consumer newspaper, 1975 (Box CA13)
    - Midas, consumer newspaper, 1978 (Box CA13)
    - Montreal Trust Company (Box CA13)
      - Consumer magazine, 1973-1979 (Box CA13)
      - Consumer newspaper, 1973-1979, (5 folders) (Box CA13)
      - Trade magazine, 1973-1979 (Box CA13)
    - Montreal Urban Community (Box CA14)
      - Consumer magazine, 1974-1976 (Box CA14)
      - Consumer newspaper, 1974-1976 (Box CA14)
    - Nordair (Box CA14)
      - Consumer magazine, 1975-1976 (Box CA14)
      - Consumer newspaper, 1975-1976 (Box CA14)
    - Northeast Airlines, consumer newspaper, 1961-1962 (Box CA14)
    - Northern Telecom (See also Oversize Box OV4) (Box CA14)
      - Consumer magazine, 1973-1984 (Box CA14)
      - Consumer newspaper, 1973-1974, 1976-1979, (4 folders) (Box CA14)
      - Trade magazine, 1974-1977 (Box CA14)
      - Trade newspaper, 1974-1977 (Box CA14)
    - Ocean Maid foods (Box CA14)
      - Consumer magazine, 1974-1978 (Box CA14)
      - Consumer newspaper, 1974-1978 (Box CA14)
      - Trade magazine, 1976 (Box CA14)
    - Pantene Vitamin hair tonic (Box CA14)
      - Consumer magazine, 1957-1960 (Box CA14)
      - Consumer newspaper, 1957-1958 (Box CA14)
    - Parke-Davis, trade magazine, 1973-1978 (Box CA14)
    - Peerless carpets (Box CA15)
      - Consumer magazine, 1988-1990 (Box CA15)
      - Consumer newspaper, 1988 (Box CA15)
    - PepsiCo (See also Oversize Box OV4) (Box CA15)
      - Consumer magazine, 1967-1978, (2 folders) (Box CA15)
      - Consumer newspaper, 1966-1978, (5 folders) (Box CA15)
      - Trade magazine, 1967-1970 (Box CA15)
    - Petrofina Canada, consumer newspaper, 1971-1979, (3 folders) (Box CA15)
    - Quebec Government (Box CA15)
      - Trade magazine, 1973-1979 (Box CA15)
      - Trade newspaper, 1973-1979 (Box CA15)
    - RCA Victor (See also Oversize Box OV4) (Box CA16)
      - Consumer magazine, 1960-1976, (2 folders) (Box CA16)
      - Consumer newspaper, 1960-1976, (13 folders) (Box CA16)
      - Trade magazine, 1960-1972, (3 folders) (Box CA16)
      - Trade newspaper, 1960-1964 (Box CA16)
    - Readers Digest (See also Oversize Box OV4) (Box CA17)
      - Consumer magazine, 1946-1966 (Box CA17)
      - Consumer newspaper, 1946-1979, (10 folders) (Box CA17)
      - Trade magazine, 1946-1970, (5 folders) (Box CA18)
      - Trade newspaper, 1947-1970, (2 folders) (Box CA18)
    - Reckitt and Coleman, consumer newspaper, 1949-1956 (Box CA18)
    - Remy Martin, consumer magazine, 1978-1979, 1982, (2 folders) (Box CA18)
    - R.J. Reynolds foods (Box CA18)
      - Consumer newspaper, 1969-1970 (Box CA18)
      - Trade magazine, 1969-1970 (Box CA18)
    - Robin Hood, multiple foods (See also Oversize Box OV4) (Box CA18)
      - Consumer magazine, 1970-1975 (Box CA18)
      - Consumer newspaper, 1970-1974 (Box CA18)
      - Trade magazine 1974-1976 (Box CA18)
      - Trade newspaper, 1973 (Box CA18)
    - Schenley Canada Gibsons Finest, consumer magazine, 1990 (Box CA18)
    - Scott Paper (See also Oversize Box OV4) (Box CA18)
      - Consumer magazine, 1964-1977, (3 folders) (Box CA18)
      - Consumer newspaper, 1964-1979, (3 folders) (Box CA18)
    - Signal Companies (Box CA18)
      - Consumer magazine, 1961-1975 (Box CA18)
      - Consumer newspaper, 1968-1971 (Box CA18)
    - Singer (See also Oversize Box OV4) (Box CA19)
      - Consumer magazine, 1964-1973 (Box CA19)
      - Consumer newspaper, 1963-1965, 1969-1973, (6 folders) (Box CA19)
      - Trade magazine, 1969 (Box CA19)
    - Smith and Nephew, consumer magazine, 1977-1979, 1982, (2 folders) (Box CA19)
    - Standard Brands (See also Oversize Box OV4) (Box CA20)
      - Chase and Sanborn (instant coffee), 1950-1970, (12 folders) (Box CA20)
      - Chase and Sanborn (regular grind) (Box CA20)
        - Consumer magazine, 1942-1970, (3 folders) (Box CA20)
        - Consumer newspaper, 1940-1949, (6 folders) (Box CA20)
        - Consumer newspaper, 1950-1963, (7 folders) (Box CA21)
        - Trade magazine, 1940-1969, (3 folders) (Box CA21)
      - Corporate and multiple products, 1944-1970, (11 folders) (Box CA21)
      - Fleischmann corporate and multiple products, 1940-1966, (10 folders) (Box CA22)
      - Fleischmann's Arkady, 1949-1955 (Box CA22)
      - Fleischmann's baking powder, 1950-1960 (Box CA22)
      - Fleischmann's Best yeast, 1956-1967 (Box CA22)
      - Fleischmann's Panomalt syrup, 1949-1961 (Box CA22)
      - Fleischmann's Tastex, 1960 (Box CA22)
      - Fleischmann's yeast (Box CA23)
        - Consumer magazine, 1940-1970, (17 folders) (Box CA23)
        - Consumer newspaper, 1940-1970, (21 folders) (Box CA24)
        - Trade magazine, 1940-1969, (7 folders) (Box CA25)
      - Magic baking powder (Box CA25)
        - Consumer magazine, 1940-1966, (15 folders) (Box CA25)
        - Consumer newspaper, 1940-1967, (9 folders) (Box CA26)
        - Trade magazine, 1940-1959 (Box CA26)
      - Magic baking soda, 1946 (Box CA26)
      - Siesta coffee, 1958, (2 folders) (Box CA26)
    - SWAKARA Furs (Box CA27)
      - Consumer magazine, 1966 (Box CA27)
      - Consumer newspaper, 1965-1966 (Box CA27)
      - Trade magazine, 1965-1966 (Box CA27)
    - Terasses, Les, consumer newspaper, 1976 (See also Oversize Box OV4) (Box CA27)
    - Toyo Spinning Company (Box CA27)
      - Consumer magazine, 1957-1959 (Box CA27)
      - Consumer newspaper, 1957-1959 (Box CA27)
      - Trade magazine, 1957-1959 (Box CA27)
    - Uncle Ben's Foods (Box CA27)
      - Consumer newspaper, 1969 (Box CA27)
      - Trade magazine, 1970 (Box CA27)
    - W.F. Young (Box CA27)
      - Consumer magazine, 1940-1978, (5 folders) (Box CA27)
      - Consumer newspaper, 1941-1979, (3 folders) (Box CA27)
      - Trade magazine, 1948-1949 (Box CA27)
    - Westmount Realties, consumer newspaper, 1959-1960 (Box CA27)
  - Toronto Office (Box CA27)
    - Bank of Montreal, 1982 (Box CA27)
    - Bank of Nova Scotia, 1963 (Box CA27)
    - Champion Spark Plug, 1963, 1986 (Box CA27)
    - Chesebrough-Pond's, 1921-1932, (9 folders) (Box CA28)
    - Chesebrough-Pond's, 1933-1941, 1959-1963, (10 folders) (Box CA29)
    - Crown Life, 1986 (Box CA30)
    - DeBeers, 1984, 1987 (Box CA30)
    - Discovery Channel, 1997 (Box CA30)
    - Ford Motor Company, 1977-1983 (See also Oversize Box OV5), (2 folders) (Box CA30)
    - Goodyear, 1982 (Box CA30)
    - [IBM: See Oversize Box OV5] (Box CA30)
    - Kraft (Philadelphia cream cheese, Lunchables, Swiss water, peanut butter, Bull's Eye barbecue sauce), 1998-1999, (2 folders) (Box CA30)
    - Labatt's, 1981-1983 (See also Oversize Box OV5, Oversize Folder OF11) (Box CA30)
    - Levi-Strauss, Great West Garment Company, 1985 (Box CA30)
    - [Mattel: See Oversize Box OV5] (Box CA30)
    - McGuiness Distillers Ltd. (Blue Nun, Silhouette Vodka), 1982 (Box CA30)
      [See also Nabisco Brands and Allied Lyons PLC in other countries]
    - [Mead Johnson: See Oversize Box OV5] (Box CA30)
    - Midas (I.C. Industries), 1982 (Box CA30)
    - Nabisco Brands, 1963 (Box CA30)
      [See also Standard Brands in other countries]
    - Northern Telecom/Bell Canada, 1987-1990 (See also Oversize Box OV5) (Box CA30)
    - PWA Inc. (Wardair), 1989 (Box CA30)
    - PepsiCo, 1982-1987 (See also Oversize Box OV5) (Box CA30)
    - R.J. Reynolds (See also Oversize Box OV5) (Box CA30)
      - Export A Ultra Light Regular, Export Light, 1988 (Box CA30)
      - Macdonald Select, 1982 (Box CA30)
      - Macdonald Special, 1987-1988 (Box CA30)
      - Tempo, 1985 (Box CA30)
      - Vantage, 1988 (Box CA30)
    - Ralston Purina (Puppy Chow and Tender Vittles), 1988 (Box CA30)
    - Royal Canadian Mist, 1985 (Box CA30)
    - Sperry Rand Corporation, 1979 (Box CA30)
    - Teledyne Water Pik, 1984, 1990 (See also Oversize Box OV5), (2 folders) (Box CA30)
    - Toronto Blue Jays, 1988 (Box CA30)
    - Toshiba, 1982, 1988 (See also Oversize Box OV5) (Box CA30)
    - Unilever, Wisk (Sam Spade campaign), 1984 (Box CA30)
    - Warner-Lambert (See also Oversize Box OV5) (Box CA30)
      - Parke-Davis (Box CA30)
        - Benglin and Sinutab, 1988-1989 (Box CA30)
        - Glycerine suppositories, 1987 (Box CA30)
      - Warner-Lambert Canada (Box CA30)
        - Listerine, 1933-1989, (4 folders) (Box CA30)
  - Vancouver Office (Box CA30)
    - ALCAN Aluminum Ltd., 1981 (Box CA30)
    - B.C. Packers (Clover Leaf tuna), 1990 (Box CA30)
    - British Columbia Development Corporation, 1982 (Box CA30)
    - Computer Associates, 1990 (Box CA30)
    - Labatt's, 1984 (See also Oversize Box OV5, Oversize Folder OF11) (Box CA30)
    - Scott Paper Company, 1984, 1990 (See also Oversize Box OV5, Oversize Folder OF11), (2 folders) (Box CA30)
  - Undetermined Office (Box CA30)
    - Lever Brothers, 1925-1927 (Box CA30)
    - United Way, 1988-1989? (Negatives) (Box CA30)
- Europe Series, 1900-2002 and undated (Box CA30)
  - Austria (Vienna Office) (Box CA30)
    - Ford, 1981, 1987 (Box EU1)
    - ICL computers, 1987 (Box EU1)
    - Jacobs AG (Nacht und Tag) coffee, 1981 (Box EU1)
    - Kraft/Oscar Mayer, 1998 (Box EU1)
  - Belgium (Box EU1)
    - Antwerp Office (Box EU1)
      - Unilever (Elidor) shampoo, 1960-1961 (Box EU1)
    - Brussels Office (Box EU1)
      - AES word processor, 1981 (Box EU1)
      - CGR cement, 1988 (Box EU1)
      - Charles Woeste Residence, 1985 (Box EU1)
      - Compagne Liebig bouillon cubes, 1969 (Box EU1)
      - Continental Foods NV (Kwatta) chocolate, 1981 (Box EU1)
      - David Campari SPA liqueur, 1983 (Box EU1)
      - DeBeers, 1984 (Box EU1)
      - Ford (Box EU1)
        - Baby seats, 1984 (Box EU1)
        - Cargo trucks, 1985 (Box EU1)
        - Escort, 1981-1982 (Box EU1)
        - Fiesta, 1982, 1985-1986 (Box EU1)
        - Sierra, 1982, 1984 (Box EU1)
      - [Gillette: See Oversize Box OV6] (Box EU1)
      - Hunter Douglas (Luxalon) office products, 1988 (Box EU1)
      - IBM, 1984-1985 (Box EU1)
      - ICL computers, 1984-1985 (See also Oversize Box OV6) (Box EU1)
      - Ippa banking, 1988, 1990 (Box EU1)
      - J. Walter Thompson Company, 1985 (Box EU1)
      - Kellogg's (Box EU1)
        - Coco Pops, undated (Box EU1)
        - Corn Flakes, 1983-1984, 1987 (Box EU1)
        - Crunchy Nut Corn Flakes, 1983-1984 (Box EU1)
        - Frosties, 1988 (Box EU1)
        - Honey Pops, 1988 (Box EU1)
        - Pro-Grain, 1988-1989 (Box EU1)
        - Rice Krispies, 1984, 1988 (Box EU1)
        - Smacks, 1988 (Box EU1)
      - Kraft (Box EU1)
        - Baika, 1984-1985 (Box EU1)
        - Doram, 1985 (Box EU1)
        - La Sante cottage cheese, 1981 (Box EU1)
        - Miracoli pasta, 1984-1985 (Box EU1)
        - Philadelphia cream cheese, 1984-1985 (Box EU1)
        - Santane low-fat foods, 1984-1985, 1989 (Box EU1)
        - Valoval, 1984-1985 (Box EU1)
        - Ziz, 1981 (Box EU1)
      - [Lever: See Oversize Folder OF12] (Box EU1)
      - Monnaie Royale de Belgique, 1990 (Box EU1)
      - [More O'Ferrall: See Oversize Box OV6] (Box EU1)
      - Pepsi Company, 1988 (Box EU1)
      - Philips home appliances, 1981-1982, 1985, 1987-1988 (See also Oversize Box OV6) (Box EU1)
      - R.J. Reynolds (Winston) cigarettes, 1989 (Box EU1)
      - S.G.G.S.E.M.F. (Vichy) mineral water, 1988 (Box EU1)
      - Sloan Sport bandages, 1989 (Box EU1)
      - Societe Generale de Banque, undated (Box EU1)
      - Teissire (Soifs Legeres) fruit cocktail syrup, 1989 (Box EU1)
      - Texaco, 1984-1985 (Box EU1)
      - Titex (Champion) sneakers, 1988 (Box EU1)
      - Toshiba, 1990 (Box EU1)
      - Toyota (See also Oversize Box OV6) (Box EU1)
        - Celica, 1988-1989 (Box EU1)
        - Minivans, 1988 (Box EU1)
        - Pre-Delivery Organization, 1988 (Box EU1)
        - Starlet, 1988-1990 (Box EU1)
      - Unilever (Calve) desserts, 1988 (Box EU1)
      - Valle d'Aosta, 1989-1990 (Box EU1)
      - Visibility Billboard Advertising, 1989 (Box EU1)
      - Warner-Lambert (Box EU1)
        - Benylin, 1989 (Box EU1)
        - Chiclets, 1989 (Box EU1)
        - Clarks gum, 1989 (Box EU1)
        - Clorets, 1988 (Box EU1)
        - Schick, 1989 (Box EU1)
        - Trident, 1988 (Box EU1)
    - Undetermined Office (Box EU1)
      - Chesebrough-Pond's, 1962 (Box EU1)
  - Czech Republic (Undetermined Office) (Box EU1)
    - Kraft (Dadek, Jacobs coffee), 1998-1999 (Box EU1)
  - Denmark (Copenhagen Office) (Box EU1)
    - American Brands cigarettes (Box EU2)
      - Cecil, 1982, 1984 (Box EU2)
      - Cook, 1980, 1982, 1984-1985 (Box EU2)
      - Savoy, 1981-1982, 1984 (Box EU2)
    - Bacardi Corporation, 1988 (Box EU2)
    - Codan Livente, 1985 (See also Oversize Box OV6) (Box EU2)
    - Commercial Leasing A/S, 1982 (Box EU2)
    - Commodore International computers, 1988 (See also Oversize Box OV6) (Box EU2)
    - [Computerland: See Oversize Box OV6] (Box EU2)
    - Dansk Kaffe, 1987 (Box EU2)
    - Denmark's Nature Preservation, 1988 (Box EU2)
    - Eastman Kodak Instamatic camera, 1972 (Box EU2)
    - Ford (Sierra), 1986 (See also Oversize Box OV6) (Box EU2)
    - Foreningen af Yngre Loeger, 1984 (Box EU2)
    - International Spike, Inc. (Jobe's) fertilizer, 1985 (Box EU2)
    - J. Walter Thompson Company, 1979-1980 (Box EU2)
    - Kraft (Box EU2)
      - Miracle Whip, 1980s (Box EU2)
      - Miracoli, 1980, 1985-1986 (Box EU2)
      - Party dip, 1980s (Box EU2)
      - Salad dressings, 1986, 1988 (Box EU2)
    - Mateus wine, 1982 (Box EU2)
    - Rambler cigarettes, 1984 (Box EU2)
    - Rolex, 1984, 1986 (Box EU2)
    - Tobaksgruppen or Tobaksindustrien, advertisements against tobacco regulation, 1981 (Box EU2)
    - Unilever (Box EU2)
      - Andy liquid cleaner, 1982 (Box EU2)
      - Lux soap, 1982 (Box EU2)
    - Unknown client, Public service campaign, We Can All Make the World a Little Better, 1987 (Box EU2)
  - Europe (Multiple Offices) (Box EU2)
    - Eastman Kodak consumer advertisements, 1962, 1965 (Box EU2)
  - Finland (Helsinki Office) (Box EU2)
    - Huhtamaki Oy (Box EU2)
      - Jalostaja pre-prepared foods, 1985 (Box EU2)
      - Jalostaja-Kennel dog food, 1987 (Box EU2)
      - Polarcup/Marimekko paper products, 1987 (Box EU2)
    - Rolex, 1986 (See also Oversize Box OV6) (Box EU2)
    - Tampella (Tend), 1986 (Not a JWT client) (Box EU2)
  - France (Box EU2)
    - Lyon Office (Box EU2)
      - Black & Decker power tools, 1982 (Box EU3)
      - [Euro Advertising: See Oversize Folder OF12] (Box EU3)
      - [Farmicredit: See Oversize Folder OF12] (Box EU3)
      - Ilford film, 1982 (Box EU3)
      - Val Thorens Tourism, 1982 (Box EU3)
    - Paris Office (Box EU3)
      - Accor hotels and catering services, 1984 (See also Oversize Box OV6) (Box EU3)
      - Agricole and Mutuel Bank (Eurocard, Mastercard), 1985-1991 (Box EU3)
      - Automobile Club National, 1991 (Box EU3)
      - [Banque Robeco: See Oversize Box OV6] (Box EU3)
      - Bernard Loisirs lawnmowers, 1989 (Box EU3)
      - Brother office equipment, 1989 (See also Oversize Box OV6) (Box EU3)
      - [Chesebrough-Pond's: See Oversize Box OV6] (Box EU3)
      - Chronopost courier services, 1987-1989 (Box EU3)
      - Conté Velleda (with Kid Coleur), 1991 (Box EU3)
      - DeBeers, 1980-1991 (See also Oversize Box OV6), (2 folders) (Box EU3)
      - DEDAL, 1991 (Box EU3)
      - Dore Dore children's clothes, 1985-1987 (Box EU3)
      - Eastman Kodak, 1993 (Box EU3)
      - Ford (See also Oversize Box OV6) (Box EU3)
        - Escort XR3, 1981 (Box EU3)
        - Fiesta, 1981, 1984 (Box EU3)
        - Probe, 1984 (Box EU3)
        - Sierra, 1984 (Box EU3)
      - Fusano ski wear, 1983 (Box EU3)
      - Gazelle cosmetics, 1986 (See also Oversize Box OV6) (Box EU3)
      - Graff jewelry, 1982 (Box EU3)
      - Guerlain cosmetics and perfumes, 1987 (Box EU3)
      - Guiness beer, 1980 (Box EU3)
      - J. Walter Thompson Company, 1987 (See also Oversize Box OV6) (Box EU3)
      - Jack Daniels, 1991 (Box EU3)
      - Kellogg Company (Box EU3)
        - Corn Flakes, 1981 (Box EU3)
        - Frosti, 1981 (Box EU3)
        - Krispi, circa 1985 (Box EU3)
        - Smacks, 1982 (Box EU3)
      - Kilimager (Klim Bebes) baby clothing, 1986 (Box EU3)
      - Lamborghini tractors, undated (Box EU3)
      - [Nadine Sampson: See Oversize Box OV6] (Box EU3)
      - Nestlé (Findus Cuisine Legere) frozen dinners, 1985 (Box EU3)
      - Outboard Marine (Evinrude) motors, 1970 (Box EU3)
      - [Penchinal: See Oversize Box OV6] (Box EU3)
      - Philips home appliances, 1982 (Box EU3)
      - [Point P: See Oversize Box OV6] (Box EU3)
      - R.J. Reynolds cigarettes (See also Oversize Box OV6) (Box EU3)
        - Salem, 1990 (Box EU3)
        - Winston, 1987-1991 (Box EU3)
      - Reader's Digest, 1959 (Box EU3)
      - Rhone-Poulenc (San Fosfate) detergent, 1986-1987 (Box EU3)
      - Rolex, 1986 (Box EU3)
      - S.C.A.D. (Narta) deodorant, 1969 (Box EU3)
      - Seagram Company (Chivas Regal) scotch whiskey, 1984 (Box EU3)
      - Start Pilote motor oil, 1989 (Box EU3)
      - Unilever (Box EU3)
        - Cutex, 1981, 1990 (Box EU3)
        - Lux soap and bath products, 1990 (Box EU3)
        - Persil, 1991 (Box EU3)
      - Val Thorens, 1982 (See also Oversize Box OV6) (Box EU3)
      - Ville du Puy fashion retailer, 1984, 1986 (Box EU3)
      - Warner-Lambert (Box EU3)
        - Clorets, 1991 (Box EU3)
        - Schick, 1990 (Box EU3)
  - Germany (Box EU3)
    - Düsseldorf Office (Box EU3)
      - Asko furniture, 1984 (Box EU4)
      - Pilkington Brothers (Flachglas AG) window glass, 1985 (Box EU4)
    - Frankfurt Office (Box EU4)
      [A very small selection. For more Frankfurt Office advertisements, see the J. Walter Thompson Company. Frankfurt Office. Advertisements Collection, circa 1950-1989]
      - Alpi Seidenweberien (Alpi) ties, 1982 (Box EU4)
      - Amaretto Di Saronno, 1991 (Box EU4)
      - Commodore International computers, 1984 (Box EU4)
      - Central Marketing Association of Advertising Deutschland Blummland flower campaign, 1982 (Box EU4)
      - David Campari S.P.A. liqueurs, 1980, 1982, 1984-1986 (Box EU4)
      - DeBeers, 1972-1990, (2 folders) (Box EU4)
      - Ford (Scorpio), 1985 (Box EU4)
        [Includes foldout advertisement for Stern German Auto Show featuring Scorpio, Sierra, Orion, Fiesta models]
      - Kellogg's (Box EU4)
        - Cornflakes, 1983 (Box EU4)
        - Muslix Musli-Bar, 1985 (Box EU4)
      - Kraft (Box EU4)
        - Das Milde salad dressing, 1984 (Box EU4)
        - Jocca cottage cheese, 1984-1985 (Box EU4)
      - Molto, 1982 (Box EU4)
      - [Pillsbury: See Oversize Box OV6] (Box EU4)
      - [Pit Stop: See Oversize Box OV6] (Box EU4)
      - Rolex, 1986 (Box EU4)
      - Rustenburg Platinum Mines (platinum jewelry), 1984-1986 (Box EU4)
      - SEB (Tefal) household appliances, 1982 (Box EU4)
      - Segram Company Ltd. (Mumm brand wines and champagne), 1982, 1986 (Box EU4)
      - Stabolisierungs Fonds Fur Weine wine campaign, 1981, 1985 (Box EU4)
    - Hamburg Office (Box EU4)
      - Brockhaus Sohne KG (Brockhaus Enzyklopadie), 1987 (Box EU4)
      - [Schleswig Holstein Tourism: See Oversize Box OV6] (Box EU4)
      - Texaco, 1987 (Box EU4)
      - Unilever (Box EU4)
        - CD personal care products, 1987-1988 (Box EU4)
        - Mentadent toothpaste, 1987 (Box EU4)
    - Undetermined Office (Box EU4)
      - Chesebrough-Pond's, 1962 (Box EU4)
      - Douwe Egberts, 1998-1999 (Box EU4)
      - Friski, undated (Box EU4)
      - Kraft (Jacobs Krönung, Miracle Whip, Philadelphia Cream Cheese, 1998-1999 (Box EU4)
      - Pepsi-Cola, 1969 (Box EU4)
      - S.C. Johnson & Sons (Johnson Auto Pudding), undated (Box EU4)
      - Ustop clothing, 1983 (Box EU4)
  - Greece (Athens Office) (Box EU4)
    - Allen Office Design, 1983 (Box EU4)
    - Alma Sport S.A. (Puma) sneakers, 1982 (Box EU4)
    - Bang and Olufsen, televisions and stereo equipment, 1982 (Box EU4)
    - Cinzano vermouth, 1982 (Box EU4)
    - Damelian (Diamond Club) jewelry, 1988 (Box EU4)
    - Eastman Kodak, Gimini and Grafitti children's cameras, 1988 (Box EU4)
    - F.A. Products (soaps, shampoo, deodorant), 1982 (Box EU4)
    - Heineken, 1988 (Box EU4)
    - J. Boutaris and Sons (Naoussa Boutari) wines, 1982 (Box EU4)
    - Kraft (Milkies, Mayonnaise, 1998 (Box EU4)
    - Manos Travel System, 1982 (Box EU4)
    - Metaxa brandy, 1972 (Box EU4)
    - R.J. Reynolds (Winston) cigarettes, 1988 (Box EU4)
    - Sekap S.A. (Sekap Special) cigarettes, 1982 (Box EU4)
    - Seree Ltd. (Astor Filter) cigarettes, 1982 (Box EU4)
    - SEB (Tefal) cooking appliances, 1982 (Box EU4)
    - [Tanagraia: See Oversize Box OV6] (Box EU4)
    - Titan Cement Company S.A. (Elki Keramiki) ceramic tile, 1990 (Box EU4)
    - Unilever (Sunsilk), 1989 (Box EU4)
    - Warner-Lambert (Chiclets), 1984 (Box EU4)
  - Hungary (Budapest Office) (Box EU4)
    - Jacobs, 1998-1999 (Box EU4)
  - Italy (Box EU4)
    - Milan Office (Box EU4)
      - Alco Tuna, circa 1990s (Box EU5)
      - Augusta helicopters, 1982 (Box EU5)
      - Black and Decker, 1984 (See also Oversize Box OV6) (Box EU5)
      - Cavit wine, 1987, 1989 (Box EU5)
      - DeBeers, 1982, 1984 (See also Oversize Box OV6) (Box EU5)
      - Eastman Kodak (Box EU5)
        - Corporate, 1982 (Box EU5)
        - Ektachrome/Kodacolor slide film, 1984, 1989 (Box EU5)
        - Ektralite 5932 motion picture film, 1982 (Box EU5)
        - Gold 100 color film, 1987 (Box EU5)
        - Kodachrome/Ektachrome super-8 motion picture film, 1982 (Box EU5)
        - Kodacolor II film, 1982 (Box EU5)
        - Kodak Paper, 1984 (Box EU5)
        - Negative 5932 motion picture film, 1982 (Box EU5)
      - Flavia jewelery, 1982 (Box EU5)
      - Ford (See also Oversize Box OV6) (Box EU5)
        - Bis, 1984 (Box EU5)
        - Escort, 1982, 1984, 1987 (Box EU5)
        - Fiesta, 1984 (Box EU5)
      - [Griguasco: See Oversize Box OV6] (Box EU5)
      - Heinz (Plasmon Dietetic) baby food, 1987, 1989 (Box EU5)
      - Hoechst (Infotee) photocopier, 1982 (With documentation) (Box EU5)
      - J. Walter Thompson Company (includes condom use PSA), 1987 and undated (Box EU5)
      - Kraft (See also Oversize Box OV6) (Box EU5)
        - Jocca, 1986, 1988 (Box EU5)
        - Maman Luise, 1986 (Box EU5)
        - Mayonnaise, 1986, 1988 (Box EU5)
        - Philadelphia cream cheese, 1982, 1986, 1988 (Box EU5)
        - Sottilette, 1986, 1988 (Box EU5)
      - Matsushita (Technics) stereo equipment, 1987-1989 (See also Oversize Box OV6) (Box EU5)
      - Philips (car stereos, light bulbs), 1988 (Box EU5)